{
    "subject": "resource/The_Deluxtone_Rockets",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of The Deluxtone Rockets is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9685826897621155,
            "question": "Where is the hometown of The Deluxtone Rockets?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9218226075172424,
            "question": "Is The Deluxtone Rockets from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9189738035202026,
            "question": "What country is considered the hometown of The Deluxtone Rockets?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7687118649482727,
            "question": "The Deluxtone Rockets are from which place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7484633326530457,
            "question": "Where are The Deluxtone Rockets based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6396222710609436,
            "question": "What is the nationality of The Deluxtone Rockets?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6059126257896423,
            "question": "Which country are The Deluxtone Rockets associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5789620876312256,
            "question": "What is the home base of The Deluxtone Rockets?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.520908534526825,
            "question": "In what nation did The Deluxtone Rockets originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4436385929584503,
            "question": "Can you tell me where The Deluxtone Rockets call home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of The Deluxtone Rockets is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9149_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what nation did The Deluxtone Rockets originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9149_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the home base of The Deluxtone Rockets?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9149_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country are The Deluxtone Rockets associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9149_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9149_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the context information provided, The Deluxtone Rockets were indeed from Muskegon, Michigan, USA (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9149/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt), which is a city in the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information mentions that the band The Deluxtone Rockets originated from Muskegon, Michigan. Michigan is a state in the United States. Therefore, it supports the statement that the hometown of The Deluxtone Rockets is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}